# **ANNA PEYSIKOVA**

Web Developer | UI Designer

LinkedIn Portfolio Github Email

(720)592-4437

I AM a front-end developer with expertise in HTML, CSS, Javascript, and React, as well as UI design using Figma and Adobe InDesign. I am thrilled to be making the leap from fifteen years in the hospitality industry into full time web development and begin quenching my thirst for knowledge, utilizing my problem-solving abilities, and jumping into new challenges in the tech field.

## **Programming Skills**

HTML5 | CSS3 | SASS | Javascript | React.JS | Ruby on Rails | Github Ubuntu/Linux | VS Code | Figma | Adobe InDesign | Heroku | Netlify

#### Languages

English (Native) | Russian (Fluent) | Italian (Fluent) | Spanish (Advanced) | French (Intermediate)

# Recent Projects

Museum of Candy - A interactive deep-dive into a sweeter world

React JS, HTML, CSS, Netlify, Git

Career Compass - A fully functioning app designed to help you decide on the right career path

Ruby on Rails, HTML, SCSS, Javascript, Heroku, Git

MentorMe – An app to help connect you with a mentor in your field of choice

Ruby on Rails, HTML, SCSS, JS Stimulus, Bootstrap, JQuery, Heroku, Git

#### Education

**LeWagon** | Full stack web development bootcamp 2023 **Scrimba** | Front end web development career path 2022 Escoffier School of Culinary Arts | Food and Beverage Management 2015-2017 American Academy of Dramatic Arts | Theater and Vocal Performance 2005-2007

### **Professional Experience**

**General Manager** August 2020- December 2022 Frank and Roze Denver, CO

Led a team of 25-30 in delivering excellent customer service to guests through maintaining a

- strong floor presence, efficient delegation, and an effective teamwork mentality
- Oversaw hiring, onboarding, training and orientation for the company
- > Trained various roles to perform at a high level by writing well-designed training materials and leading skills labs throughout the year
- > Facilitated dynamic staff communication via Slack and productive team meeting schedules

#### **Food and Beverage Manager**

September 2017-May 2020

Ca'Dario Ristorante

Santa Barbara, CA

- Oversaw management team for a multi-location upscale restaurant concept
- Responsible for hiring and training of management staff
- > Achieved certified sommelier credential and implemented my knowledge to construct a higher quality wine and beverage program
- > Developed excellent collaboration and delegation skills to effectively lead multiple teams in a fast-paced environment